<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wenlong Liu&#39;s website on Wenlong Liu&#39;s website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wenlong Liu&#39;s website on Wenlong Liu&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Wenlong Liu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>usfertilizer</title>
      <link>/project/usfertilizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/usfertilizer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soil blogs in zhihu.com (in Chinese)</title>
      <link>/project/example-external-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/example-external-project/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to visualize hydrograph and chemograph in the same plot?</title>
      <link>/post/how-to-visualize-hydrograph-and-chemograph-in-the-same-plot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-to-visualize-hydrograph-and-chemograph-in-the-same-plot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently, many researchers employ R to conduct data cleaning, manipulation and visualization. Among all the R packages, ggplot2 is one of the most popular, fancy and powerful tool to visualize data. Although ggplot2 is very convenient and easy to use, it is difficult to plot data in dual y-axis. According to the comments from &lt;a href=&#34;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/3099219/plot-with-2-y-axes-one-y-axis-on-the-left-and-another-y-axis-on-the-right/3101876#3101876&#34;&gt;Hadely Wichham on June 23, 2010&lt;/a&gt;, the main developer of ggplot2, the authors of ggplot2 hold the idea that:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not possible in ggplot2 because I believe plots with separate y scales (not y-scales that are transformations of each other) are fundamentally flawed. Some problems:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The[y] are not invertible: given a point on the plot space, you can not uniquely map it back to a point in the data space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They are relatively hard to read correctly compared to other options. See &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lri.fr/~isenberg/publications/papers/Isenberg_2011_ASO.pdf&#34;&gt;A Study on Dual-Scale Data Charts&lt;/a&gt; by Petra Isenberg, Anastasia Bezerianos, Pierre Dragicevic, and Jean-Daniel Fekete for details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They are easily manipulated to mislead: there is no unique way to specify the relative scales of the axes, leaving them open to manipulation. Two examples from the Junkcharts blog: &lt;a href=&#34;http://junkcharts.typepad.com/junk_charts/2006/06/illusion_of_suc.html&#34;&gt;one&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://junkcharts.typepad.com/junk_charts/2006/05/the_crossover_l.html&#34;&gt;two&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They are arbitrary: why have only 2 scales, not 3, 4 or ten?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though there exist some concerns regarding dual y-axis plot, it is very convenient for hydrologist and environmental engineers, who focus on stream nutrient dynamics, to plot both hydrograph and chemograph in the same graph. To make the dual y-axis graph, we can use a built-in ggplot2 function, &lt;a href=&#34;http://ggplot2.tidyverse.org/reference/sec_axis.html&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;sec_axis()&lt;/em&gt; updated in Nov. 2016&lt;/a&gt;, to add second y axis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;a-reproducible-example-to-show-hydrograph-and-chemograph-in-dual-y-axis&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A reproducible example to show hydrograph and chemograph in dual y-axis&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;sec_axis()&lt;/em&gt; function is actually the projection the original y axis to a secondary axis. The tricky is to define a proper transformation function. We can use the ratio of maximum solute concentration over maximum stream discharge to transform the y axis. There is an example using the stream discharge and turbidity data from USGS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# import libraries
require(dataRetrieval)
require(ggplot2)
require(dplyr)

# information for usgs stations.
station_Id = &amp;quot;05446500&amp;quot; #Rock River Near Joslin, IL
parameter_code = c(&amp;quot;00060&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;63680&amp;quot;)  # discharge, Turbidity (Form Neph).
start_date = &amp;quot;2017-06-01&amp;quot;
end_date = &amp;quot;2017-08-01&amp;quot;

# retrieve data from usgs.
turbidity_flow = readNWISuv(siteNumbers = station_Id,
                            parameterCd = parameter_code,
                            startDate = start_date,
                            endDate = end_date)
# data cleaning.
turbidity_flow = renameNWISColumns(turbidity_flow)
param_info = attr(turbidity_flow, &amp;quot;variableInfo&amp;quot;)
site_info = attr(turbidity_flow, &amp;quot;siteInfo&amp;quot;)

# the ratio of maximum solute concentration over maximum flow.
trans_ratio = max(turbidity_flow$.HACH._Turb_Inst, na.rm = TRUE) / 
  max(turbidity_flow$Flow_Inst, na.rm = TRUE)

# plot data
ts = ggplot(turbidity_flow, aes(x = dateTime))+
  geom_point(aes(y = Flow_Inst, color = &amp;quot;Stream discharge&amp;quot;))+
  geom_line(aes(y = Flow_Inst, color = &amp;quot;Stream discharge&amp;quot;))+
  geom_point(aes(y = .HACH._Turb_Inst/trans_ratio, color = &amp;quot;Turbidity&amp;quot;))+
  geom_line(aes(y = .HACH._Turb_Inst/trans_ratio, color = &amp;quot;Turbidity&amp;quot;))+
  scale_y_continuous(name = param_info$variableDescription[1],
                     sec.axis = sec_axis(~.*trans_ratio, name = &amp;quot;Turbidity, Form Neph, HACH&amp;quot;))+
  ggtitle(site_info$station_nm)+
  labs(color = &amp;quot;Parameters&amp;quot;)+
  theme(legend.position =  c(0.15, 0.85))

ts&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/2018-05-08-how-to-visualize-hydrograph-and-chemograph-in-the-same-plot_files/figure-html/hydrograph-1.png&#34; width=&#34;672&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;further-materials&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Further materials&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The example in this blog only considers 1:1 transformation between two Axis. Sometime there are complicated conditions where the transformation formula needs more attentions. Please visit the following sites for more information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rpubs.com/MarkusLoew/226759&#34;&gt;Basic introduction of sec_axis()&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://whatalnk.github.io/r-tips/ggplot2-secondary-y-axis.nb.html&#34;&gt;More complicated plots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;references&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;References:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the information in this blog was adapted from &lt;a href=&#34;https://rpubs.com/MarkusLoew/226759&#34;&gt;Markus Loew&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://owi.usgs.gov/R/dataRetrieval.html#1&#34;&gt;DataRetrieval tutorial&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/3099219/plot-with-2-y-axes-one-y-axis-on-the-left-and-another-y-axis-on-the-right/3101876#3101876&#34;&gt;Hadley’s comments&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://ggplot2.tidyverse.org/reference/sec_axis.html&#34;&gt;Official website of sec_axis()&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights from intensive water quality sampling in a drained agriculutral field</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-04-11_wenlong_bryan_high_frequency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-04-11_wenlong_bryan_high_frequency/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Preferred citation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liu, W&lt;/strong&gt;, B Maxwell, F Birgand, M Youssef, GM Chescheir. “Insights from intensive water quality sampling in a drained agriculutral field”  Agricultural Drainage Management Systems Task Force/NCERA 217, Raleigh, April 11-12, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long-term temporal variation of nitrate concentration-stream discharge (C-Q) relationship for an agrcultural watershed in Midwest USA</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-04-11-wenlong-liu-ncera/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-04-11-wenlong-liu-ncera/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Preferred citation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liu, W&lt;/strong&gt;, S Tian, M Youssef, F Birgand, GM Chescheir. “Long-term temporal variation of nitrate concentration-stream discharge (C-Q) relationship for an agrcultural watershed in Midwest USA”  Agricultural Drainage Management Systems Task Force/NCERA 217, Raleigh, April 11-12, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brief introduction of storm hysteresis effects in solute concentration-stream discharge (C-Q) relationship</title>
      <link>/post/brief-introduction-of-storm-hysteresis-in-solute-concentration-stream-discharge-c-q-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/brief-introduction-of-storm-hysteresis-in-solute-concentration-stream-discharge-c-q-relationship/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div id=&#34;what-are-storm-hysteresis-effects&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What are storm hysteresis effects?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Generally, in order to investigate the dynamics of stream discharge and solute concentrations (C-Q relationship) in a watershed, researchers and environmental engineers usually set up monitoring stations in the watershed outlet. As the temporal dynamics of discharge and solute concentration is an integration of complex hydrological and biochemical processes, the relationship between solute concentration and discharge, hereafter called C-Q relationship, is mostly non-linear. If we plot the concentration against discharge within one storm event in a plot, we are supposed to see a non-linear loop, instead of a linear regression curve. The tweet below demonstrated the hysteresis effects in one event happened in 1991.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Bored of seeing time-series data?  Maybe there is another way of visualizing your discharge and nutrient concentration measurements in streams. &lt;a href=&#34;https://t.co/PSIEWpJp8E&#34;&gt;pic.twitter.com/PSIEWpJp8E&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Wenlong Liu (@tianya0423) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/tianya0423/status/929969875707138048?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;November 13, 2017&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src=&#34;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;how-to-describe-a-hysteresis-loop&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How to describe a hysteresis loop?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the shapes of hysteresis loops vary because of the different hydrogeochemical processes, it is important to describe a hysteresis loop to compare across spatial and temporal scales. For a fictitious hysteresis loop in Fig. 1a，adapted from &lt;span class=&#34;citation&#34;&gt;Long et al. (&lt;a href=&#34;#ref-long2017patterns&#34;&gt;2017&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;, there are three variables to characterize a loop:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Direction: the direction of loops based on time or any x-axis variable, e.g. clockwise and anti-clockwise;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amplitude: the strength of hysteresis effects;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slope: to indicate the dilution/leaching of solute during an event compared with the base flow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;figure&#34;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;/img/blog_imgs/cq_plot.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Fig. 1 Depiction of hysteresis loops&#34; /&gt;
&lt;p class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;Fig. 1 Depiction of hysteresis loops&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;why-are-we-interested-in-hysteresis-effects&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why are we interested in hysteresis effects?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the complexity of hydrogeochemical processes in the watershed, the watershed is mostly a &lt;em&gt;black box&lt;/em&gt; for us. It is impossible to identify the exact sources and reactions contributing to the nutrient export. Luckily, we can employ hysteresis effects as a proxy to internal reactions in watersheds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, &lt;span class=&#34;citation&#34;&gt;Blaen et al. (&lt;a href=&#34;#ref-blaen2017high&#34;&gt;2017&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; monitored high-frequency stream discharge and nutrients data in a headwater catchment for 8 months and delineated 29 storm events representing 31% of observation period. Based on the analysis of storm hysteresis patterns, &lt;span class=&#34;citation&#34;&gt;Blaen et al. (&lt;a href=&#34;#ref-blaen2017high&#34;&gt;2017&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; identified the key drivers and processes of nutrient export, showing in Fig. 2. Further details are available from an open-source publication &lt;a href=&#34;http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017JG003904/full&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;figure&#34;&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;/img/blog_imgs/conceptual_hysteresis.png&#34; alt=&#34;Fig. 2 Conceptual model highlighting the spatial distribution of NO3-N and DOC across the catchment and key processes that control stream nutrient export under different hydroclimatological conditions.&#34; /&gt;
&lt;p class=&#34;caption&#34;&gt;Fig. 2 Conceptual model highlighting the spatial distribution of NO3-N and DOC across the catchment and key processes that control stream nutrient export under different hydroclimatological conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the help of rapidly developing in-situ measuring techniques, we are going to gain more access to intensive measurements from different research interests. Therefore, the analysis of C-Q relationship with high-frequency dataset becomes more popular. The author, Wenlong Liu, is working on this topic right now, and going to update his latest research in this blog. Further Content will include the methods to quantify the hysteresis patterns and to identify the drivers based on various approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope this blog helps. Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;references&#34; class=&#34;section level2 unnumbered&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;References:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;refs&#34; class=&#34;references&#34;&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;ref-blaen2017high&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blaen, Phillip J, Kieran Khamis, Charlotte Lloyd, Sophie Comer-Warner, Francesco Ciocca, Rick M Thomas, A Rob MacKenzie, and Stefan Krause. 2017. “High-Frequency Monitoring of Catchment Nutrient Exports Reveals Highly Variable Storm Event Responses and Dynamic Source Zone Activation.” &lt;em&gt;Journal of Geophysical Research: Biogeosciences&lt;/em&gt; 122 (9). Wiley Online Library:2265–81.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;ref-long2017patterns&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long, David T, Thomas C Voice, Irene Xagaroraki, Ao Chen, Huiyun Wu, Eunsang Lee, Amira Oun, and Fangli Xing. 2017. “Patterns of Cq Hysteresis Loops and Within an Integrative Pollutograph for Selected Inorganic and Organic Solutes and E. Coli in an Urban Salted Watershed During Winter-Early Spring Periods.” &lt;em&gt;Applied Geochemistry&lt;/em&gt; 83. Elsevier:93–107.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High frequency measurements in a drained agricultural field</title>
      <link>/project/high_frequency_measurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/high_frequency_measurements/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In order to further investigate the water movement and nutrient transport from agricultural fields, we developed equipment and algorithms to zoom in the hydrograph and chemograph both spatially and temporally.
We installed self-designed high frequency sampling equipment to measure water quality from subsurface tile drainage outlet and from shallow groundwater.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the drainage tile outlet, we installed V-notch weir and pressure transducers to measure drainage flow, and an optical spetrophometer to continuously monitor nitrate concentration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In shallow groundwater, we digged 10  water quality wells at different locations in shallow groundwater.  The multi-point sampler collected &lt;strong&gt;fresh&lt;/strong&gt; water samples from wells every 6 minutes. In other words, we took water quality measurements in each well every hour.  The following picture shows the running device deployed in early spring, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/mps.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;A photo showing a running multi-point sampler and accessories. (MPS)&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further analysis of high frequency measurements is still undergoing to achieve the following objectives:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the temporal dynamics of drainage discharge and nitrate concentration inferred from high frequency measurements?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can we interprete the relationship between nutrient concentration and discharge in tile drainage using high frequency measurements?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to describe and predict the transport and fate of nitrate in and from agricultural fields?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Updated on May 8th, 2018)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transforming denitrifying bioreactors research and application: unveiling the inside of the blackbox</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-01-29_birgand_bioreactors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-01-29_birgand_bioreactors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Preferred citation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Birgand, F, B Maxwell, S Tian, &lt;strong&gt;W Liu&lt;/strong&gt;, L Negm, M Youssef, G Chescheir, L Schipper, L Christianson, M Helmers, D Williams. &amp;ldquo;Transforming denitrifying bioreactors research and application: unveiling the inside of the blackbox&amp;rdquo; USDA NIFA and NSF Water and Soils Meeting, Project Director Meeting, Jan. 29-31, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hellow world!</title>
      <link>/post/brand-new-personal-website-of-wenlong-liu-powered-by-hugo-academic-and-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/brand-new-personal-website-of-wenlong-liu-powered-by-hugo-academic-and-blogdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since Jan. 2018, my brand new website is published online.  The website is powered by &lt;a href=&#34;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Blogdown&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hugo-academic&lt;/a&gt;, and deployed by &lt;a href=&#34;https://pages.github.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt;.  All the codes are open to public and available at &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wenlong-liu/wenlong-website&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;my github repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I build this website to achieve two goals: helping others know more about my professional achievements, and presenting my most latest output (with details) to persons of interest. Therefore, I will list my publications, including journal articles, conference presentations and proceedings, and book chapters (if any) here.  In addition, the post section will briefly introduce my new ideas, experiences or findings. I will also upload some interesting pictures to draw more attentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I benefit a lot from open-source software and materials, except where otherwise noted, all the materials, such as blogs, picture, codes, etc., are licensed under a &lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International license&lt;/a&gt;.  Please feel free to share or adapt anything you get, as long as your follow the terms indicated in the license introduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your attentions. Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nitrate concentration-drainage flow (C-Q) relationship for a drained agricultural field in Eastern North Carolina Plain</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-01-31-wenlong-liu-agu-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-01-31-wenlong-liu-agu-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Preferred citation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liu, W&lt;/strong&gt;, M Youssef, F Birgand, GM Chescheir, B Maxwell, S Tian. “Nitrate concentration-drainage flow (C-Q) relationship for a drained agricultural field in Eastern North Carolina Plain” AGU fall meeting, New Orleans, December 11-15, 2017&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Retention Capacity of Infiltration Rain Gardens and Their Potential Effect on Urban Stormwater Management in the Sub-Humid Loess Region of China</title>
      <link>/publication/wrm_shuangcheng_tang_2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/wrm_shuangcheng_tang_2016/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimental study on geotextile envelope for subsurface drainage in Yellow River Delta</title>
      <link>/publication/tcsae_wenlong_liu_2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/tcsae_wenlong_liu_2013/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
