<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wenlong Liu&#39;s website on Wenlong Liu&#39;s website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wenlong Liu&#39;s website on Wenlong Liu&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Wenlong Liu, CC BY 4.0</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>High frequency measurements in a drained agricultural field</title>
      <link>/project/high-frequency-measurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/high-frequency-measurements/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We installed self-designed high frequency sampling equipment to measure water quality from subsurface drainage in a drained agricultural field.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>/post/brand-new-personal-website-of-wenlong-liu-powered-by-hugo-academic-and-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/brand-new-personal-website-of-wenlong-liu-powered-by-hugo-academic-and-blogdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since Jan. 2018, my brand new website is published online.  The website is powered by &lt;a href=&#34;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Blogdown&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hugo-academic&lt;/a&gt;, and deployed by &lt;a href=&#34;https://pages.github.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt;.  All the codes are open to public and available at &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wenlong-liu/wenlong-website&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;my github repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I build this website to achieve two goals: helping others know more about my professional achievements, and presenting my most latest output (with details) to persons of interest. Therefore, I will list my publications, including journal articles, conference presentations and proceedings, and book chapters (if any) here.  In addition, the post section will briefly introduce my new ideas, experiences or findings. I will also upload some interesting pictures to draw more attentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I benefit a lot from open-source software and materials, except where otherwise noted, all the materials, such as blogs, picture, codes, etc., are licensed under a &lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International license&lt;/a&gt;.  Please feel free to share or adapt anything you get, as long as your follow the terms indicated in the license introduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your attentions. Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nitrate concentration-drainage flow (C-Q) relationship for a drained agricultural field in Eastern North Carolina Plain</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-01-31-wenlong-liu-agu-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-01-31-wenlong-liu-agu-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Preferred citation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liu, W&lt;/strong&gt;, M Youssef, F Birgand, GM Chescheir, B Maxwell, S Tian. “Nitrate concentration-drainage flow (C-Q) relationship for a drained agricultural field in Eastern North Carolina Plain” AGU fall meeting, New Orleans, December 11-15, 2017&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Retention Capacity of Infiltration Rain Gardens and Their Potential Effect on Urban Stormwater Management in the Sub-Humid Loess Region of China</title>
      <link>/publication/wrm_shuangcheng_tang_2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/wrm_shuangcheng_tang_2016/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimental study on geotextile envelope for subsurface drainage in Yellow River Delta</title>
      <link>/publication/tcsae_wenlong_liu_2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/tcsae_wenlong_liu_2013/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
