<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C-Q relationship on Wenlong Liu&#39;s website</title>
    <link>/tags/c-q-relationship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in C-Q relationship on Wenlong Liu&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Wenlong Liu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/c-q-relationship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantification of storm hysteresis effects in C-Q relationship</title>
      <link>/post/quantification-of-storm-hysteresis-effects-in-c-q-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/quantification-of-storm-hysteresis-effects-in-c-q-relationship/</guid>
      <description>The need to quantify hysteresis effects    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brief introduction of storm hysteresis effects in solute concentration-stream discharge (C-Q) relationship</title>
      <link>/post/brief-introduction-of-storm-hysteresis-in-solute-concentration-stream-discharge-c-q-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/brief-introduction-of-storm-hysteresis-in-solute-concentration-stream-discharge-c-q-relationship/</guid>
      <description>What are storm hysteresis effects? Generally, in order to investigate the dynamics of stream discharge and solute concentrations (C-Q relationship) in a watershed, researchers and environmental engineers usually set up monitoring stations in the watershed outlet. As the temporal dynamics of discharge and solute concentration is an integration of complex hydrological and biochemical processes, the relationship between solute concentration and discharge, hereafter called C-Q relationship, is mostly non-linear. If we plot the concentration against discharge within one storm event in a plot, we are supposed to see a non-linear loop, instead of a linear regression curve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High frequency measurements in a drained agricultural field</title>
      <link>/project/high_frequency_measurements/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/high_frequency_measurements/</guid>
      <description>In order to further investigate the water movement and nutrient transport from agricultural fields, we developed equipment and algorithms to zoom in the hydrograph and chemograph both spatially and temporally. We installed self-designed high frequency sampling equipment to measure water quality from subsurface tile drainage outlet and from shallow groundwater.
At the drainage tile outlet, we installed V-notch weir and pressure transducers to measure drainage flow, and an optical spetrophometer to continuously monitor nitrate concentration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>