<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks on Wenlong Liu&#39;s website</title>
    <link>/talk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks on Wenlong Liu&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Wenlong Liu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/talk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights from intensive water quality sampling in a drained agriculutral field</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-04-11_wenlong_bryan_high_frequency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-04-11_wenlong_bryan_high_frequency/</guid>
      <description>Preferred citation:
Liu, W, B Maxwell, F Birgand, M Youssef, GM Chescheir. “Insights from intensive water quality sampling in a drained agriculutral field” Agricultural Drainage Management Systems Task Force/NCERA 217, Raleigh, April 11-12, 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long-term temporal variation of nitrate concentration-stream discharge (C-Q) relationship for an agrcultural watershed in Midwest USA</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-04-11-wenlong-liu-ncera/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-04-11-wenlong-liu-ncera/</guid>
      <description>Preferred citation:
Liu, W, S Tian, M Youssef, F Birgand, GM Chescheir. “Long-term temporal variation of nitrate concentration-stream discharge (C-Q) relationship for an agrcultural watershed in Midwest USA” Agricultural Drainage Management Systems Task Force/NCERA 217, Raleigh, April 11-12, 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transforming denitrifying bioreactors research and application: unveiling the inside of the blackbox</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-01-29_birgand_bioreactors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-01-29_birgand_bioreactors/</guid>
      <description>Preferred citation:
Birgand, F, B Maxwell, S Tian, W Liu, L Negm, M Youssef, G Chescheir, L Schipper, L Christianson, M Helmers, D Williams. &amp;ldquo;Transforming denitrifying bioreactors research and application: unveiling the inside of the blackbox&amp;rdquo; USDA NIFA and NSF Water and Soils Meeting, Project Director Meeting, Jan. 29-31, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nitrate concentration-drainage flow (C-Q) relationship for a drained agricultural field in Eastern North Carolina Plain</title>
      <link>/talk/2018-01-31-wenlong-liu-agu-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/2018-01-31-wenlong-liu-agu-2017/</guid>
      <description>Preferred citation:
Liu, W, M Youssef, F Birgand, GM Chescheir, B Maxwell, S Tian. “Nitrate concentration-drainage flow (C-Q) relationship for a drained agricultural field in Eastern North Carolina Plain” AGU fall meeting, New Orleans, December 11-15, 2017</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>